<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mental Health on Disconnected</title>
    <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/categories/mental-health/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mental Health on Disconnected</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</webMaster>
    <copyright>Copyright Lucrèce Skylar Næss 2018.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 02:04:04 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/categories/mental-health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Maintaining Lighthouses</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/lighthouses/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 02:04:04 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/lighthouses/</guid>
      <description>I feel like maintaing hope is analogous to maintaining the light in a lighthouse. I try to maintain hope to feel like I&amp;rsquo;ve accomplished something, or to keep optimistic. I don&amp;rsquo;t maintain hope solely for myself though, I do it for others, so that in dark times they may see as a guiding light. A reason not to give up quite yet, and to carry on. Sometimes I do maintain hope for selfish reasons though, hoping for something to happen, or for someone to come back when I know it won&amp;rsquo;t happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post DPDR</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/post-dpdr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 01:44:25 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/post-dpdr/</guid>
      <description>My experience with DPDR is only that now, an experience. While it has shaped who I am, I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t say it dominates my life. What does dominate my life is the fact that I&amp;rsquo;m still in the closet about being trans (MtF). The only people who really know are typically close friends, and it&amp;rsquo;s not for a lack of support. My parents would most likely totally support me, it&amp;rsquo;s more-so crippling anxiety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After DPDR</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/after-dpdr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 02:53:58 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/after-dpdr/</guid>
      <description>DPDR used to be something that weighed me down, but after 6 or so years of struggling to understand how I could possibly deal with it, It surprisingly became less and less bothersome seemingly on its own. This isn&amp;rsquo;t to say I haven&amp;rsquo;t learned quite a bit along the way, but at the same time it didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like I was actively trying to get rid of my DP. I think learning mindfulness was a big part of the recovery process for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Background Noise</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/background-noise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 15:28:28 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/background-noise/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes depersonalization makes me feel like I&amp;rsquo;m no more than background noise. The sense of detatchment from my surroundings socially, but not physically leads to me observing quite a bit instead of interacting. I think this may be part of the reason I enjoy &amp;ldquo;people watching&amp;rdquo; so much, (walking around and just observing people) because it gives me an opportunity to just forget I exist. While Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s blissful to feel like unimportant background noise, at other times it&amp;rsquo;s crippling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foolish Panic</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/foolish-panic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 03:10:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/foolish-panic/</guid>
      <description>More than a month later I know recognize how foolish my initial panic was when it came to what happened with Ace, though perhaps not entirely preventable. It reminds me of years ago when I was much younger and how I&amp;rsquo;d over-dramatically panic in reaction to something upsetting. While there is a small amout of regret for the actions I took, it&amp;rsquo;s ultimately not the end of the world. I think sometimes we need to remind ourselves that even when something truamatic happens and it feels as though everything comes to a crashing halt, the world around you is still going on just as it always has, and will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foolish Bravado?</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/foolish-bravado/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 19:35:01 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/foolish-bravado/</guid>
      <description>I was foolish&amp;hellip;oh so foolish, to think nothing would come of that week with Ace. To think I&amp;rsquo;d just walk away scot-free was laughable, I&amp;rsquo;m far too fragile for that to have been the outcome. Now I can&amp;rsquo;t even say sorry and explain why. I let Ace think he wouldn&amp;rsquo;t hurt me, I let him think things would change, and maybe they haven&amp;rsquo;t, and maybe I&amp;rsquo;ve just been overreacting to all of this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chasing Intimacy</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/chasing-intimacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 04:12:22 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/chasing-intimacy/</guid>
      <description>Preface This post heavily depends on you having read the previous. post.
Escapism I&amp;rsquo;ve always felt like I was missing something, and for the longest while I&amp;rsquo;ve tried to fill that void with intimacy, or sex. Perhaps recklessly so, regardless I&amp;rsquo;ve had a string of partners, Some good, some bad, and some just selfish attempts to forget. Though sometimes trying to forget has just led to deepening my scars. While I&amp;rsquo;ve changed quite a bit over the years, I still find myself trying to fill that empty void.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sex, is Sex: NSFW</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/sex-is-sex/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 03:49:46 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/sex-is-sex/</guid>
      <description>Preface So, I guess this one is going to be a heavy one, or perhaps I just think I&amp;rsquo;m going to be deep. I had a sexual experience for the first time in a while, though this time it was accompanied by a horrifyingly heavy bout of dissociation. During and after sex I was thrown into a horribly uncomfortable detachment from &amp;ldquo;myself&amp;rdquo;. To make things easier (and for privacy), I&amp;rsquo;ll refer to the friend I had sex with as &amp;ldquo;Ace&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Racing Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/racing-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 08:35:07 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/racing-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>A Curse and a Blessing For me, racing thoughts are a double edged sword. On one hand, it allows for fast reaction time, but it also never really stops. My thoughts are like a train without breaks. Until I hit the bed and pass out, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t stop. Like many things, I&amp;rsquo;ve grown somewhat accustom to it.
Another downside of having racing thoughts is that when I think about something negative, my brain often latches on and won&amp;rsquo;t let go of the thought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding The Words</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/finding-the-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 04:28:20 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/finding-the-words/</guid>
      <description>A bit of Preface For years, I&amp;rsquo;ve always struggled to put into words, what exactly DPDR made me feel. Then, I stumbled upon a post on r/dpdr that for the most part, put it into words, perfectly, this post was written by u/lunar_limbo.
The Train That Hit Me  I have always held great empathy. To the point I would be overcome by others stories. I would live them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Chilling Lack of Discomfort Part 1</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/a-chilling-lack-of-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 02:59:46 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/a-chilling-lack-of-1/</guid>
      <description>Depersonalization and being Transgender. A lack of identity, and feeling psychically disconnected from my body, combined with a sense of being born the wrong gender presents an interesting mix of feelings, or lack thereof. Normally one would expect a transgender person to be unhappy with their birth sex, and yes, while I&amp;rsquo;m generally dissatisfied being in a male body, over the years the feeling that I&amp;rsquo;m &amp;ldquo;connected&amp;rdquo; with my physical body has more or less eroded away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feeling Comfortable</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/feeling-comfortable/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2017 02:07:18 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/feeling-comfortable/</guid>
      <description>A bit of a problem Anyone who&amp;rsquo;s read any of my previous posts will know that I&amp;rsquo;m dissatisfied with my gender. There are some aspects of being a male that don&amp;rsquo;t appeal to me personally. As a possible solution, I&amp;rsquo;ve thought about hormone therapy as an avenue to resolving my gender dysphoria. This is a difficult decision to make, not so much because I don&amp;rsquo;t want to do it, but rather the heavy and permanent consequences associated with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trust</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/trust/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 01:20:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/trust/</guid>
      <description>Preface This is a continuation of a previous post, wherein we talked about trust.
Information I&amp;rsquo;m less trusting then I&amp;rsquo;d honestly like to admit. While I feel I can tell certain close friends some things, I feel as though I can&amp;rsquo;t tell them other things. Mostly do to feeling self conscious, or not wanting them to find something out about me. There are a fair few people even in my inner circle of friends who I would not tell that this blog exists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dysphoria Continued: NSFW</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/dysphoria-continued/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 01:58:46 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/dysphoria-continued/</guid>
      <description>Limbo For the past few days I&amp;rsquo;ve found myself in a sort of uncomfortable limbo, stuck between the want to abandon a gender which offers me little comfort, and identity I have no connection to, or to stick with my current gender in fear of the social stigmas I may face. Stuck between a rock and a hard place, uncertain what to do.
Trapped Ironically, it&amp;rsquo;s not my sexual organs that bring my discomfort when it comes to my gender.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Identity and Dissociation</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/identity-and-dissociation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 02:03:09 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/identity-and-dissociation/</guid>
      <description>Identity, and Names A beautiful quote form a Disqus Blog post. In fact I find the quote quite aptly describes me. For example, I detest my birth name. While people I know in real life use it, when online friends refer to me by my online pseudonym, for some reason I find it less jarring.
If I had to guess, the reason for this is because the majority of friends I&amp;rsquo;ve made throughout my life, have been online, so my sense of identity online strengthened while I dissociated from my real identity more and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Space: NSFW</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/personal-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2017 03:37:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/personal-space/</guid>
      <description>Preface This is going to be another post that just rambles.
A bit of context I prefer, most of the time, to not have my personal space violated, I&amp;rsquo;d assume this is the norm among the majority of people. For me it stems from trust issues that I&amp;rsquo;ve had for quite a while now. I won&amp;rsquo;t scream or pitch a fight if my personal space is violated, rather I try to tell the person who violated it not to make the same mistake again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dysphoria: NSFW</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/dysphoria/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 01:55:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/dysphoria/</guid>
      <description>Preface: NSFW. This one might get weird, and rambly. That&amp;rsquo;s the difficulty with writing about things you don&amp;rsquo;t remember clearly.
What is Gender Dysphoria? As not everybody reading this might know what gender dysphoria is right off, I&amp;rsquo;ll try to provide a simple definition. Gender dysphoria is a condition where a person emotionally and psychologically identifies as the opposite of one&amp;rsquo;s biological sex. E.g.
 A person who is biologically male would identify as female.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>