<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>relationships on Disconnected</title>
    <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/tags/relationships/</link>
    <description>Recent content in relationships on Disconnected</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright Lucrèce Skylar Næss 2021</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 04:27:40 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/tags/relationships/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Casual Sex and Emotional Investment</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/casual-sex-and-emotional-investment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 04:27:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/casual-sex-and-emotional-investment/</guid>
      <description>In past posts where I wrote about sex and the horrible truamatic epxeriences and thoughts that followed it, I often expressed a great deal of dread and anxiety. Usually while writing them I was in a panic, my mind racing at incredible speeds. I now write with a steady hand, and a calm, clear mind.
Casual sex can be great, it can allow you to relieve pent up desires, to be intimate with another person, to bond even more with someone else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maintaining Lighthouses</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/lighthouses/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 02:04:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/lighthouses/</guid>
      <description>I feel like maintaing hope is analogous to maintaining the light in a lighthouse. I try to maintain hope to feel like I&amp;rsquo;ve accomplished something, or to keep optimistic. I don&amp;rsquo;t maintain hope solely for myself though, I do it for others, so that in dark times they may see as a guiding light. A reason not to give up quite yet, and to carry on. Sometimes I do maintain hope for selfish reasons though, hoping for something to happen, or for someone to come back when I know it won&amp;rsquo;t happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chasing Exhaustion</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/chasing-exhaustion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 02:45:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/chasing-exhaustion/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been emotionally exhausted for quite a while. After being seemingly ghosted by my most recent partner, I just don&amp;rsquo;t feel anything. Sure for a while I did feel sad and such, but, now I just feel tired. I suppose going from one relationship to the next has grown old. I&amp;rsquo;d rather cherish strong meaningful friendships at the moment. I really have no incentive to jump head-first into yet another relationship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Do I Do?</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/what-do-i-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 05:15:37 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/what-do-i-do/</guid>
      <description>Cesc has my heart, but I feel we&amp;rsquo;re too different. The first major difference between us I can think of is that Cesc wants kids and I really don&amp;rsquo;t, I guess another thing that has perturbed me before about Cesc is that they&amp;rsquo;ve told me I&amp;rsquo;m not feminine in appearance enough, which while sadly true, still felt hurtful. I can&amp;rsquo;t blame someone for having preferences though. I guess I&amp;rsquo;m just love-sick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Identity and Dissociation</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/identity-and-dissociation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 02:03:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/identity-and-dissociation/</guid>
      <description>Identity, and Names A beautiful quote form a Disqus Blog post. In fact I find the quote quite aptly describes me. For example, I detest my birth name. While people I know in real life use it, when online friends refer to me by my online pseudonym, for some reason I find it less jarring.
If I had to guess, the reason for this is because the majority of friends I&amp;rsquo;ve made throughout my life, have been online, so my sense of identity online strengthened while I dissociated from my real identity more and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Space: NSFW</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/personal-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2017 03:37:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/personal-space/</guid>
      <description>Preface This is going to be another post that just rambles.
A bit of context I prefer, most of the time, to not have my personal space violated, I&amp;rsquo;d assume this is the norm among the majority of people. For me it stems from trust issues that I&amp;rsquo;ve had for quite a while now. I won&amp;rsquo;t scream or pitch a fight if my personal space is violated, rather I try to tell the person who violated it not to make the same mistake again.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
