<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Disconnected</title>
    <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Disconnected</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</webMaster>
    <copyright>Copyright Lucrèce Skylar Næss 2017. Powered by Hugo.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 01:58:46 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dysphoria Continued: NSFW</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/dysphoria-continued/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 01:58:46 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/dysphoria-continued/</guid>
      <description>Limbo For the past few days I&amp;rsquo;ve found myself in a sort of uncomfortable limbo, stuck between the want to abandon a gender which offers me little comfort, and identity I have no connection to, or to stick with my current gender in fear of the social stigmas I may face. Stuck between a rock and a hard place, uncertain what to do.
Trapped Ironically, it&amp;rsquo;s not my sexual organs that bring my discomfort when it comes to my gender.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Identity and Dissociation</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/identity-and-dissociation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 02:03:09 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/identity-and-dissociation/</guid>
      <description>Identity, and Names A beautiful quote form a Disqus Blog post. In fact I find the quote quite aptly describes me. For example, I detest my birth name. While people I know in real life use it, when online friends refer to me by my online pseudonym, for some reason I find it less jarring.
If I had to guess, the reason for this is because the majority of friends I&amp;rsquo;ve made throughout my life, have been online, so my sense of identity online strengthened while I dissociated from my real identity more and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Night owl woes</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/night-owl-woes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2017 01:35:01 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/night-owl-woes/</guid>
      <description>I thought I&amp;rsquo;d write something a bit less heavy this time. I&amp;rsquo;m a &amp;ldquo;night owl&amp;rdquo;, which if you don&amp;rsquo;t know what that means, I basically am awake mostly in the afternoon and at very late hours in the night / early morning (the opposite of most people). I also happen to live in a small town (ironically, the larget in my county), so there&amp;rsquo;s really nothing much to do at night since the town is &amp;ldquo;dead&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Space: NSFW</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/personal-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2017 03:37:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/personal-space/</guid>
      <description>Preface This is going to be another post that just rambles.
A bit of context I prefer, most of the time, to not have my personal space violated, I&amp;rsquo;d assume this is the norm among the majority of people. For me it stems from trust issues that I&amp;rsquo;ve had for quite a while now. I won&amp;rsquo;t scream or pitch a fight if my personal space is violated, rather I try to tell the person who violated it not to make the same mistake again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dysphoria: NSFW</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/dysphoria/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 01:55:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/dysphoria/</guid>
      <description>Preface: NSFW. This one might get weird, and rambly. That&amp;rsquo;s the difficulty with writing about things you don&amp;rsquo;t remember clearly.
What is Gender Dysphoria? As not everybody reading this might know what gender dysphoria is right off, I&amp;rsquo;ll try to provide a simple definition. Gender dysphoria is a condition where a person emotionally and psychologically identifies as the opposite of one&amp;rsquo;s biological sex. E.g.
 A person who is biologically male would identify as female.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boop</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/boop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2017 02:34:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/boop/</guid>
      <description>First initial test post.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>