<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ace and I on Disconnected</title>
    <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/series/ace-and-i/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ace and I on Disconnected</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright Lucrèce Skylar Næss 2021</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 03:10:32 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/series/ace-and-i/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Foolish Panic</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/foolish-panic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 03:10:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/foolish-panic/</guid>
      <description>More than a month later I know recognize how foolish my initial panic was when it came to what happened with Ace, though perhaps not entirely preventable. It reminds me of years ago when I was much younger and how I&amp;rsquo;d over-dramatically panic in reaction to something upsetting. While there is a small amout of regret for the actions I took, it&amp;rsquo;s ultimately not the end of the world. I think sometimes we need to remind ourselves that even when something truamatic happens and it feels as though everything comes to a crashing halt, the world around you is still going on just as it always has, and will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foolish Bravado?</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/foolish-bravado/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 19:35:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/foolish-bravado/</guid>
      <description>I was foolish&amp;hellip;oh so foolish, to think nothing would come of that week with Ace. To think I&amp;rsquo;d just walk away scot-free was laughable, I&amp;rsquo;m far too fragile for that to have been the outcome. Now I can&amp;rsquo;t even say sorry and explain why. I let Ace think he wouldn&amp;rsquo;t hurt me, I let him think things would change, and maybe they haven&amp;rsquo;t, and maybe I&amp;rsquo;ve just been overreacting to all of this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chasing Intimacy</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/chasing-intimacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 04:12:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/chasing-intimacy/</guid>
      <description>Preface This post heavily depends on you having read the previous. post.
Escapism I&amp;rsquo;ve always felt like I was missing something, and for the longest while I&amp;rsquo;ve tried to fill that void with intimacy, or sex. Perhaps recklessly so, regardless I&amp;rsquo;ve had a string of partners, Some good, some bad, and some just selfish attempts to forget. Though sometimes trying to forget has just led to deepening my scars. While I&amp;rsquo;ve changed quite a bit over the years, I still find myself trying to fill that empty void.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sex, is Sex: NSFW</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/sex-is-sex/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 03:49:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/sex-is-sex/</guid>
      <description>Preface So, I guess this one is going to be a heavy one, or perhaps I just think I&amp;rsquo;m going to be deep. I had a sexual experience for the first time in a while, though this time it was accompanied by a horrifyingly heavy bout of dissociation. During and after sex I was thrown into a horribly uncomfortable detachment from &amp;ldquo;myself&amp;rdquo;. To make things easier (and for privacy), I&amp;rsquo;ll refer to the friend I had sex with as &amp;ldquo;Ace&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
