<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Identity on Disconnected</title>
    <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/tags/identity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Identity on Disconnected</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</webMaster>
    <copyright>Copyright Lucrèce Skylar Næss 2017. Powered by Hugo.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 04:28:20 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/tags/identity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding The Words</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/finding-the-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 04:28:20 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/finding-the-words/</guid>
      <description>A bit of Preface For years, I&amp;rsquo;ve always struggled to put into words, what exactly DPDR made me feel. Then, I stumbled upon a post on r/dpdr that for the most part, put it into words, perfectly, this post was written by u/lunar_limbo.
The Train That Hit Me  I have always held great empathy. To the point I would be overcome by others stories. I would live them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Chilling Lack of Discomfort Part 1</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/a-chilling-lack-of-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 02:59:46 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/a-chilling-lack-of-1/</guid>
      <description>Depersonalization and being Transgender. A lack of identity, and feeling psychically disconnected from my body, combined with a sense of being born the wrong gender presents an interesting mix of feelings, or lack thereof. Normally one would expect a transgender person to be unhappy with their birth sex, and yes, while I&amp;rsquo;m generally dissatisfied being in a male body, over the years the feeling that I&amp;rsquo;m &amp;ldquo;connected&amp;rdquo; with my physical body has more or less eroded away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feeling Comfortable</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/feeling-comfortable/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2017 02:07:18 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/feeling-comfortable/</guid>
      <description>A bit of a problem Anyone who&amp;rsquo;s read any of my previous posts will know that I&amp;rsquo;m dissatisfied with my gender. There are some aspects of being a male that don&amp;rsquo;t appeal to me personally. As a possible solution, I&amp;rsquo;ve thought about hormone therapy as an avenue to resolving my gender dysphoria. This is a difficult decision to make, not so much because I don&amp;rsquo;t want to do it, but rather the heavy and permanent consequences associated with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Identity and Dissociation</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/identity-and-dissociation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 02:03:09 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/identity-and-dissociation/</guid>
      <description>Identity, and Names A beautiful quote form a Disqus Blog post. In fact I find the quote quite aptly describes me. For example, I detest my birth name. While people I know in real life use it, when online friends refer to me by my online pseudonym, for some reason I find it less jarring.
If I had to guess, the reason for this is because the majority of friends I&amp;rsquo;ve made throughout my life, have been online, so my sense of identity online strengthened while I dissociated from my real identity more and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dysphoria: NSFW</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/dysphoria/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 01:55:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc (Lucrèce Skylar Næss)</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/dysphoria/</guid>
      <description>Preface: NSFW. This one might get weird, and rambly. That&amp;rsquo;s the difficulty with writing about things you don&amp;rsquo;t remember clearly.
What is Gender Dysphoria? As not everybody reading this might know what gender dysphoria is right off, I&amp;rsquo;ll try to provide a simple definition. Gender dysphoria is a condition where a person emotionally and psychologically identifies as the opposite of one&amp;rsquo;s biological sex. E.g.
 A person who is biologically male would identify as female.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>