<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>emotions on Disconnected</title>
    <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/tags/emotions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in emotions on Disconnected</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright Lucrèce Skylar Næss 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 04:27:40 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/tags/emotions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Casual Sex and Emotional Investment</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/casual-sex-and-emotional-investment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 04:27:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/casual-sex-and-emotional-investment/</guid>
      <description>In past posts where I wrote about sex and the horrible truamatic epxeriences and thoughts that followed it, I often expressed a great deal of dread and anxiety. Usually while writing them I was in a panic, my mind racing at incredible speeds. I now write with a steady hand, and a calm, clear mind.
Casual sex can be great, it can allow you to relieve pent up desires, to be intimate with another person, to bond even more with someone else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chasing Exhaustion</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/chasing-exhaustion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 02:45:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/chasing-exhaustion/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been emotionally exhausted for quite a while. After being seemingly ghosted by my most recent partner, I just don&amp;rsquo;t feel anything. Sure for a while I did feel sad and such, but, now I just feel tired. I suppose going from one relationship to the next has grown old. I&amp;rsquo;d rather cherish strong meaningful friendships at the moment. I really have no incentive to jump head-first into yet another relationship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Do I Do?</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/what-do-i-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 05:15:37 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/what-do-i-do/</guid>
      <description>Cesc has my heart, but I feel we&amp;rsquo;re too different. The first major difference between us I can think of is that Cesc wants kids and I really don&amp;rsquo;t, I guess another thing that has perturbed me before about Cesc is that they&amp;rsquo;ve told me I&amp;rsquo;m not feminine in appearance enough, which while sadly true, still felt hurtful. I can&amp;rsquo;t blame someone for having preferences though. I guess I&amp;rsquo;m just love-sick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foolish Panic</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/foolish-panic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 03:10:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/foolish-panic/</guid>
      <description>More than a month later I know recognize how foolish my initial panic was when it came to what happened with Ace, though perhaps not entirely preventable. It reminds me of years ago when I was much younger and how I&amp;rsquo;d over-dramatically panic in reaction to something upsetting. While there is a small amout of regret for the actions I took, it&amp;rsquo;s ultimately not the end of the world. I think sometimes we need to remind ourselves that even when something truamatic happens and it feels as though everything comes to a crashing halt, the world around you is still going on just as it always has, and will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foolish Bravado?</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/foolish-bravado/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 19:35:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/foolish-bravado/</guid>
      <description>I was foolish&amp;hellip;oh so foolish, to think nothing would come of that week with Ace. To think I&amp;rsquo;d just walk away scot-free was laughable, I&amp;rsquo;m far too fragile for that to have been the outcome. Now I can&amp;rsquo;t even say sorry and explain why. I let Ace think he wouldn&amp;rsquo;t hurt me, I let him think things would change, and maybe they haven&amp;rsquo;t, and maybe I&amp;rsquo;ve just been overreacting to all of this.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>