<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Disconnected</title>
    <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Disconnected</description>
    <generator>Hugo - gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <contact>lucrecenaess@airmail.cc</contact>
    <copyright>Copyright Lucrèce Skylar Næss 2018</copyright>
    
        <atom:link href="https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Casual Sex and Emotional Investment</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/casual-sex-and-emotional-investment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 04:27:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Lucrèce Skylar Næss</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/casual-sex-and-emotional-investment/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
      <content>&lt;p&gt;In past posts where I wrote about sex and the horrible truamatic epxeriences and
thoughts that followed it, I often expressed a great deal of dread and anxiety.
Usually while writing them I was in a panic, my mind racing at incredible
speeds. I now write with a steady hand, and a calm, clear mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Casual sex can be great, it can allow you to relieve pent up desires, to be
intimate with another person, to bond even more with someone else. That being
said, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t come without risk, emotional investment is an important
compononent of any sexual relationship, no-matter the length. Emotional
investment can be anything from the bond of friendship, to loving the other
person. Emotional investment isn&amp;rsquo;t, and shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a one-way street though,
when it is, it can lead to either you or the other person becoming hurt.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maintaining Lighthouses</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/lighthouses/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 02:04:04 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Lucrèce Skylar Næss</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/lighthouses/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
      <content>&lt;p&gt;I feel like maintaing hope is analogous to maintaining the light in a
lighthouse. I try to maintain hope to feel like I&amp;rsquo;ve accomplished something, or
to keep optimistic. I don&amp;rsquo;t maintain hope solely for myself though, I do it for
others, so that in dark times they may see as a guiding light. A reason not to
give up quite yet, and to carry on. Sometimes I do maintain hope for selfish
reasons though, hoping for something to happen, or for someone to come back when
I know it won&amp;rsquo;t happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When this happens I tend to put a lot of effort into maintaining that
lighthouse, only to be disappointed no ships find my light. Sometimes we have
to realize though that once certain ships set sale, they won&amp;rsquo;t come back.
Whether they became lost along the way, or simply chose a different path, we
have to accept that we won&amp;rsquo;t see them again. We have to be cognizant of the fact
that not everything will happen the way we want it to. When a relationship
crumbles, or a romantic interest doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel the same way you do. Instead of
hoping things will change, and then being disappointed when they don&amp;rsquo;t, we
just have to accept sometimes some things are just the way they are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Investing hope into the wrong things can become a vicious cycle, and subject you
to a rollercoaster of emotions. I&amp;rsquo;ve made that mistake plenty of times, and came
out the other end utterly exhausted. This doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean let bad storms keep you
from maintaining your lighthouse though, you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t want one (or more)
event(s) to cause you to let the light in your lighthouse go out. In conclusion,
don&amp;rsquo;t let your hope fade, but don&amp;rsquo;t pour too much hope into certain things
either.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post DPDR</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/post-dpdr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 01:44:25 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Lucrèce Skylar Næss</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/post-dpdr/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
      <content>

&lt;p&gt;My experience with DPDR is only that now, an experience. While it has shaped
who I am, I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t say it dominates my life. What does dominate my life is the
fact that I&amp;rsquo;m still in the closet about being trans (MtF). The only people who
really know are typically close friends, and it&amp;rsquo;s not for a lack of support. My
parents would most likely totally support me, it&amp;rsquo;s more-so crippling anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;mutism&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;Mutism&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a rather introverted person and sometimes I find it hard to say&amp;hellip;well,
anything really. At times it even gets to the point where I desperately want to
say something, but my body physically prevents me from doing so. This combined
with intrusive thoughts can make communication very difficult, because the
intrusive thoughts will fill me with doubt which only adds more fuel to the
fire. Making me less likely, or physically capable of being able to say what I
want(ed) to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;intrusive-thoughts&#34;&gt;Intrusive Thoughts&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whenever I think about telling my parents I&amp;rsquo;m trans my mind always jumps to
thoughts like:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What if they don&amp;rsquo;t accept me?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What if they get irrationally upset?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What if they don&amp;rsquo;t accept my new name?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which ultimately leads me to not wanting to tell them because these thoughts
will just pile up and stress me out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;social-optics&#34;&gt;Social optics&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve always been closer to my friends than my family, and often feel I have more
familial ties with certain close friends than I do my biological family. This
generally makes me less willing to talk about my life with my family because
I&amp;rsquo;m just not all that close to them and would rather keep most of my life to
myself.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After DPDR</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/after-dpdr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 02:53:58 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Lucrèce Skylar Næss</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/after-dpdr/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
      <content>&lt;p&gt;DPDR used to be something that weighed me down, but after 6 or so years of
struggling to understand how I could possibly deal with it, It surprisingly
became less and less bothersome seemingly on its own. This isn&amp;rsquo;t to say I
haven&amp;rsquo;t learned quite a bit along the way, but at the same time it didn&amp;rsquo;t feel
like I was actively trying to get rid of my DP. I think learning mindfulness
was a big part of the recovery process for me. I now need to work on my other
problems like social anxiety, and self image.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chasing Exhaustion</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/chasing-exhaustion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 02:45:49 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Lucrèce Skylar Næss</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/chasing-exhaustion/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
      <content>

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been emotionally exhausted for quite a while. After being seemingly ghosted
by my most recent partner, I just don&amp;rsquo;t feel anything. Sure for a while I did
feel sad and such, but, now I just feel tired. I suppose going from one
relationship to the next has grown old. I&amp;rsquo;d rather cherish strong meaningful
friendships at the moment. I really have no incentive to jump head-first into
yet another relationship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;observations-from-tired-eyes&#34;&gt;Observations From Tired Eyes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This in in stark contrast to a close friend of mine. They&amp;rsquo;re looking to get into
a relationships with someone, which there&amp;rsquo;s nothing wrong with that. Though as
they&amp;rsquo;ve been talking to me, their desperation has become abundantly clear.
After not having someone in 2 years I can understand wanting to jump back in,
but, what I&amp;rsquo;ve seen it do to them is terrible. The spectrum of emotions I
sometimes see within the span of a few hours or days terrifies me. They can go
from feeling hopelessly melancholy to being on top of the world, to annoying if
not sometimes scary levels of anger. Going from one emotional extreme to the
next isn&amp;rsquo;t healthy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remember going through a very similar thing myself, but, I eventually grew
out of it. Becoming sick of the repeated heartbreak. To be fair though, my
experience was drawn out over a number of years and relationships.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Do I Do?</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/what-do-i-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 05:15:37 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Lucrèce Skylar Næss</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/what-do-i-do/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Cesc has my heart, but I feel we&amp;rsquo;re too different. The first major difference
between us I can think of is that Cesc wants kids and I &lt;strong&gt;really&lt;/strong&gt; don&amp;rsquo;t, I
guess another thing that has perturbed me before about Cesc is that they&amp;rsquo;ve told
me I&amp;rsquo;m not feminine in appearance enough, which while sadly true, still felt
hurtful. I can&amp;rsquo;t blame someone for having preferences though. I guess I&amp;rsquo;m just
love-sick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Honestly I don&amp;rsquo;t even know if I&amp;rsquo;m genuinely attracted to Cesc or if they just
gave me something I was sorely craving.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Background Noise</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/background-noise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 15:28:28 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Lucrèce Skylar Næss</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/background-noise/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Sometimes depersonalization makes me feel like I&amp;rsquo;m no more than background
noise. The sense of detatchment from my surroundings socially, but not
physically leads to me observing quite a bit instead of interacting. I think
this may be part of the reason I enjoy &amp;ldquo;people watching&amp;rdquo; so much, (walking
around and just observing people) because it gives me an opportunity to just
forget I exist. While Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s blissful to feel like unimportant
background noise, at other times it&amp;rsquo;s crippling. I feel lost and ignored in the
sea of noise.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foolish Panic</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/foolish-panic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 03:10:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Lucrèce Skylar Næss</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/foolish-panic/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
      <content>

&lt;p&gt;More than a month later I know recognize how foolish my initial panic was when
it came to what happened with Ace, though perhaps not entirely preventable. It reminds me of years ago when I was much younger and how I&amp;rsquo;d over-dramatically
panic in reaction to something upsetting. While there is a small amout of regret
for the actions I took, it&amp;rsquo;s ultimately not the end of the world. I think
sometimes we need to remind ourselves that even when something truamatic happens
and it feels as though everything comes to a crashing halt, the world around you
is still going on just as it always has, and will.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;time&#34;&gt;Time&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s taken time for my mind to fully comprehend all of what happened with Ace,
but I&amp;rsquo;m glad to say for the most part it no longer haunts me. Rather my memories
of hanging out with Ace are warm ones, sans my crippling panic attack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;reflection&#34;&gt;Reflection&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I wrote my last blog post I was in the mindset that writing more blog posts
would help, yet what really helped was a bit of a nostolgia trip. Sometime after
my last blog post I become more and more concerned with my personal identity and
who I was, an issue that&amp;rsquo;s haunted me all of my life. The way I went about this
was just going through archives of what had to be hundreds of emails I had with
old freinds and acquaintances, seeing how I&amp;rsquo;ve grown as a person over the years.
It&amp;rsquo;s actually amazing how much I&amp;rsquo;ve changed as a person! Though that is a post
for another time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;summary&#34;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, I&amp;rsquo;ve learned a lot about not only myself over the past few
months, but I&amp;rsquo;ve learned how to handle certain situations that may happen again.
I&amp;rsquo;m glad I spent the time with Ace that I did.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foolish Bravado?</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/foolish-bravado/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 19:35:01 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Lucrèce Skylar Næss</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/foolish-bravado/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
      <content>

&lt;p&gt;I was foolish&amp;hellip;oh so foolish, to think nothing would come of that week with Ace.
To think I&amp;rsquo;d just walk away scot-free was laughable, I&amp;rsquo;m far too fragile for
that to have been the outcome. Now I can&amp;rsquo;t even say sorry and explain why. I let
Ace think he wouldn&amp;rsquo;t hurt me, I let him think things would change, and maybe
they haven&amp;rsquo;t, and maybe I&amp;rsquo;ve just been overreacting to all of this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;regret&#34;&gt;Regret&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the time I had reassured Ace nothing would change and that he wouldn&amp;rsquo;t hurt
me, in hindsight that was a grave mistake. Now I&amp;rsquo;m having flashbacks,
daydreaming, having panic attacks, and generally overthinking about the whole
thing. I know it&amp;rsquo;s just my mind trying to process everything that happened, but
it&amp;rsquo;s hard to not feel like it was something that could&amp;rsquo;ve been easily avoided.
I&amp;rsquo;m sorry I&amp;rsquo;ve been rambling about this whole thing for a total of 3 posts, but
that&amp;rsquo;s how much this has been getting to me. It&amp;rsquo;s something that is constantly
on my mind. I have no reason to apologize to Ace, I really owe no one an apology
besides myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;apologies&#34;&gt;Apologies&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned being sorry and wanting to apologize a few times throughout this
post without really providing propper context first. What initially brought on
this panic attack and subsuquent rambling post was a simple few words.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m really sorry, for everything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I typed it without even thinking really, something deep inside me just knew to
type the words. Ace of course, asked what I was sorry about, reading his reply
released a torrent of emotions. The ensuing flood of emotions and thoughts caused
me to sieze up. I wanted so desperately to tell him why&amp;hellip;but I just ended up
just backing out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nvm&amp;ndash;I wasn&amp;rsquo;t in the right frame of mind when I typed that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At that point I was dealing with a full blown panic attack and didn&amp;rsquo;t really
take in much of what Ace had said after that. I ended up just going to bed,
hoping to sleep off the panic attack.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chasing Intimacy</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/chasing-intimacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 04:12:22 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Lucrèce Skylar Næss</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/chasing-intimacy/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
      <content>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;preface&#34;&gt;Preface&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This post heavily depends on you having read the
&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/disconnected/post/sex-is-sex/&#34;&gt;previous&lt;/a&gt;. post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;escapism&#34;&gt;Escapism&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve always felt like I was missing something, and for the longest while I&amp;rsquo;ve
tried to fill that void with intimacy, or sex. Perhaps recklessly so, regardless
I&amp;rsquo;ve had a string of partners, Some good, some bad, and some just selfish
attempts to forget. Though sometimes trying to forget has just led to deepening
my scars. While I&amp;rsquo;ve changed quite a bit over the years, I still find myself
trying to fill that empty void. Escapism is a dangerous rabbit-hole that is hard
to crawl back out of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;lust&#34;&gt;Lust&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve tried to senselessly fuck the pain away many times, flinging myself towards
whoever was willing. Obviously though sex is only a temporary relief from my
real problems. Nonetheless I now find myself in a bit of an odd position. I
had sex with Ace, it was quite the traumatic experience, yet I find myself
wanting to masochistically fling myself back at him. Whenever I think about him
I feel nauseous, and I begin to derealize a bit. My mind not wanting me to
relive what happened before, yet at the same time wanting to do it again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;ace&#34;&gt;Ace&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose my relationship with Ace is kinda, &amp;ldquo;complex&amp;rdquo; now. At first Ace and I
were just close friends. Previously I had told Ace I had feelings for him, but
he he didn&amp;rsquo;t feel the same about me, so it never went anywhere. Though as time
went on Ace began to question himself more and had come to a point where he felt
as though he had feelings for me, but he wasn&amp;rsquo;t completely sure. What happened
next was a few days of cuddling, kissing, and general messing around. Then as
soon as it had started and I had flung myself head-first into senseless passion,
it seemingly ended. Now I find myself selfishly craving more. I guess I&amp;rsquo;m back
where I started, just close friends, and feeling a bit dejected over Ace&amp;rsquo;s lack
of interest in me.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sex, is Sex: NSFW</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/sex-is-sex/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 03:49:46 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Lucrèce Skylar Næss</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/sex-is-sex/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
      <content>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;preface&#34;&gt;Preface&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, I guess this one is going to be a heavy one, or perhaps I just think I&amp;rsquo;m
going to be deep. I had a sexual experience for the first time in a while,
though this time it was accompanied by a horrifyingly heavy bout of
dissociation. During and after sex I was thrown into a horribly uncomfortable
detachment from &amp;ldquo;myself&amp;rdquo;. To make things easier (and for privacy), I&amp;rsquo;ll refer to
the friend I had sex with as &amp;ldquo;Ace&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;open-relationships&#34;&gt;Open Relationships&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Various relationships I&amp;rsquo;ve had exposed me to some interesting ways to think of
intimacy, relationships, sex, and other things. I won&amp;rsquo;t beat around the bush,
Ace isn&amp;rsquo;t my partner, and some people may consider that cheating. Some people
may think you can only love and be intimate with one individual and that
intimacy is black and white. Some of the people I&amp;rsquo;ve had relationships with made
me challenge these ideas. Also I&amp;rsquo;m currently in an open-relationship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I personally don&amp;rsquo;t think love and intimacy are black and white, I prefer to
think of them as spectrums. The love you have for a best friend perhaps isn&amp;rsquo;t
the same as the love you have for your partner, but it&amp;rsquo;s still something strong
that bonds you two together. I suppose having mostly open-relationships has
caused me to have this view. I suppose I justify having sex with Ace by the
measure of how attached I am to him. I&amp;rsquo;m never as attached to Ace as much as I
am attached to my partner. I may cuddle, kiss, have sex with Ace, very much-so
like I do with my partner, but the degree of intimacy is vastly different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;reflection&#34;&gt;Reflection&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been 5-6 days since I last started writing this post, and I&amp;rsquo;ve had even
more time to think back on my experience. I now realize I can blame no one but
myself for the way I had felt. Even though dissociation is usually out of my
control, I could&amp;rsquo;ve done things to make the experience more pleasant. Perhaps
this is wrong but, I feel if I had let myself be more intimate with Ace, then
perhaps it would&amp;rsquo;ve helped me to cut through some of the &amp;ldquo;brain fog&amp;rdquo; that I was
experiencing. Of course I realize this two or so weeks after, and now yearn to
fix my mistake. Though realistically it&amp;rsquo;s not one I&amp;rsquo;ll probably ever get to fix,
and will just have to be something I learn from.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;intimacy&#34;&gt;Intimacy&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I honestly wish I had put in more of an honest effort to be intimate with Ace,
The rather mechanical nature of sex combined with the horrible side-effects of
depersonalization sucked the enjoyment right out of the experience. The lack of
kissing before sex probably led to me feeling more disconnected, something I
honestly should&amp;rsquo;ve done, at the time I was nervous. Unlike previous sexual
experiences where I had been riding an intoxicating euphoric rush, this was
devoid of that. I also regret not telling him I love him. Words have always been
hard for me, even with people I&amp;rsquo;m very close to. At times I get so anxious I
feel like I physically can&amp;rsquo;t speak. I&amp;rsquo;m still learning and realizing new things
to be honest, even though it happened what feels like so long ago now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose the worst part is, I probably won&amp;rsquo;t have another chance to make up for
the mistakes I made with Ace. I suppose I shouldn&amp;rsquo;t let it haunt me, but the
experience in general was just very traumatic. It has opened my eyes and made me
think about my life quite a bit though. I began to realize things I hadn&amp;rsquo;t
before, though perhaps that is for another blog post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;dissociation-and-sex&#34;&gt;Dissociation and Sex&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose this will be a bit of a chronicle of the events that happened, and how
dissociation played a role. I woke up in Ace&amp;rsquo;s bed, I had spent the night with
him. I vaguely remember cuddling him and starting out with a bit of foreplay. At
that moment, I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel dissociated what-so-ever, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t awake enough yet
for my brain to kick in fully. After a bit of foreplay Ace and I stripped, he
handed me a condom, I accidentally broke it while trying to put it on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At that moment, It hit me, lightly at first but then like a train later. A
flare up of DPDR. Ace helped me put a condom on and proceeded to lay down on his
stomach for me. I adequately lubed myself and Ace up, crawling on top of him. I
gently eased myself inside him and began slowly thrusting. At which point It
became pretty much nothing but mechanical for me, I thrusted, moaned breathily,
even girlishly moaned his name&amp;hellip;but I felt no emotion. He was crying out and
moaning my name, it was really cute but&amp;hellip;I was able to enjoy none of it. I kept
at it until he came, but wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to get myself to cum. After that I just
pulled out and laid on my back on the bed, staring up at the ceiling. My mind
reeling from the intense flare up of DPDR, I was panting, the sensory fog
was&amp;ndash;like nothing I had felt before. I almost couldn&amp;rsquo;t talk&amp;hellip;I was only able to
mutter out simple replies. My mind had thrown me under the bus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even quite a while after sex, my mind was still retreated into a dissociative
cocoon. I felt unsatisfied, regretful, and craved for affection. If I remember
correctly, for the rest of that day I was just in this horrid hyper-dissociated
state&amp;hellip;barely able to talk. The only thing that kept me from crying was the
sheer lack of emotion. I now realize I should&amp;rsquo;ve told him I was uncomfortable
and I was having a DPDR flare up, and not have had sex right then. Instead I
just pushed past it, thinking it was a bit of anxiety that would clear up. I
ended up traumatizing myself for quite a bit and have learned a lesson. Even
though it&amp;rsquo;s been what feels like so long ago now, I&amp;rsquo;m still realizing and
reflecting upon new things. Don&amp;rsquo;t make the same mistake I did, if you have any
type of mental health issue crop up during or before sex, and you want to stop,
then stop. There&amp;rsquo;s absolutely no shame to that, your mental health is top
priority.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Racing Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/racing-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 08:35:07 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Lucrèce Skylar Næss</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/racing-thoughts/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
      <content>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-curse-and-a-blessing&#34;&gt;A Curse and a Blessing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me, racing thoughts are a double edged sword. On one hand, it allows for
fast reaction time, but it also never really stops. My thoughts are like a train
without breaks. Until I hit the bed and pass out, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t stop. Like many
things, I&amp;rsquo;ve grown somewhat accustom to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another downside of having racing thoughts is that when I think about something
negative, my brain often latches on and won&amp;rsquo;t let go of the thought. Which
causes me to overthink things quite often. It&amp;rsquo;s usually harmful and causes me
added stress.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding The Words</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/finding-the-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 04:28:20 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Lucrèce Skylar Næss</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/finding-the-words/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
      <content>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-bit-of-preface&#34;&gt;A bit of Preface&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For years, I&amp;rsquo;ve always struggled to put into words, what exactly DPDR made me
feel. Then, I stumbled upon a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reddit.com/r/dpdr/comments/6ktual/vent_chronic_dp_since_childhood_has_stripped_all/&#34;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reddit.com/r/dpdr&#34;&gt;r/dpdr&lt;/a&gt; that for the most part, put
it into words, perfectly, this post was written by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reddit.com/user/lunar_limbo&#34;&gt;u/lunar_limbo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-train-that-hit-me&#34;&gt;The Train That Hit Me&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have always held great empathy. To the point I would be overcome by others stories. I would live them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This, the first thing after the preface, tugged at my heart strings right away.
I instantly connected with luna right here, for throughout the years I&amp;rsquo;ve had
DPDR, while feeling robbed of my own feelings, I was always able to empathize
with others on a level I never saw among my peers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am nothing. Merely a reflecting pond for others to find meaning in their lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For years I&amp;rsquo;ve tried to help others with their lives, hoping someday to find
some way to make my own better, but in doing so, largely only ended up helping
others. A sad consequence of this has been the further erosion of my own
identity. In that sense, I too am merely a reflection pond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am incapable of holding healthy people&amp;rsquo;s attention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While for me, not entirely true (as I&amp;rsquo;ve learned to mesh into social
environments). It still resonates with me because of my own social
difficulties I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered due to DPDR.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DP killed me before I ever had a chance. I can only cope inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This, a snippet of the penultimate paragraph is what really hit home for me,
what made me feel I wasn&amp;rsquo;t entirely alone. I too feel like DPDR silently
stripped my identity from me, before I was able to ever solidify it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;thanks&#34;&gt;Thanks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can not put into words how greatful I am for stumbling upon luna&amp;rsquo;s post, it
laid to rest the struggle for words I have tried to find for so long.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiatus</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/hiatus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 03:05:56 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Lucrèce Skylar Næss</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/hiatus/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
      <content>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;hey&#34;&gt;Hey&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry I went on a huge hiatus, to anyone who was reading and expected a normal
flow of content, it must&amp;rsquo;ve been quite the smack in the face. I&amp;rsquo;ll try to get
back to regular content.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Chilling Lack of Discomfort Part 1</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/a-chilling-lack-of-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 02:59:46 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Lucrèce Skylar Næss</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/a-chilling-lack-of-1/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
      <content>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;depersonalization-and-being-transgender&#34;&gt;Depersonalization and being Transgender.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lack of identity, and feeling psychically disconnected from my body,
combined with a sense of being born the wrong gender presents an interesting
mix of feelings, or lack thereof. Normally one would expect a transgender person
to be unhappy with their birth sex, and yes, while I&amp;rsquo;m generally dissatisfied
being in a male body, over the years the feeling that I&amp;rsquo;m &amp;ldquo;connected&amp;rdquo; with my
physical body has more or less eroded away. This has created a very warped sense
of how I perceive my body, my body is less-so &amp;ldquo;me&amp;rdquo;, and more-so just a vessel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I view my consciousness and body as separate, and while this lends me a certain
amount of comfort, it also often leads to odd quirks. One example is looking in
the mirror, when I look in the mirror it&amp;rsquo;s typically a very jarring experience
as my mind seems to reject the body I&amp;rsquo;m in and sometimes perceives my reflection
as a different person.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feeling Comfortable</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/feeling-comfortable/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2017 02:07:18 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Lucrèce Skylar Næss</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/feeling-comfortable/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
      <content>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-bit-of-a-problem&#34;&gt;A bit of a problem&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone who&amp;rsquo;s read any of my previous posts will know that I&amp;rsquo;m dissatisfied with
my gender. There are some aspects of being a male that don&amp;rsquo;t appeal to me
personally. As a possible solution, I&amp;rsquo;ve thought about hormone therapy as an
avenue to resolving my gender dysphoria. This is a difficult decision to make,
not so much because I don&amp;rsquo;t want to do it, but rather the heavy and permanent
consequences associated with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;commitment&#34;&gt;Commitment&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Transitioning (no pun intended) is a lifelong commitment, and not something you
can really go back on all the way. It&amp;rsquo;s important to know that &lt;strong&gt;you&lt;/strong&gt; want to
make this commitment and stick with it. That you can fully embrace you decision,
that being said, decisions like these don&amp;rsquo;t come without apprehension. Though
I&amp;rsquo;m sure my apprehension will my relieved once I star transition to a body I
feel more comfortable with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;social-impact&#34;&gt;Social Impact&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The social reactions of people who find out you&amp;rsquo;re trans, or am planning on
transitioning can either be heart-warming, or bone-chilling (or anything in
between really). My worst fear though would be my parents disowning me. While
I&amp;rsquo;ve never been particularly close with my family, it&amp;rsquo;d just deepen the rift I
already feel. Luckily all the friends I&amp;rsquo;ve told have been very supportive of me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;everyday-crap&#34;&gt;Everyday crap&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With (at the time of writing this) the recent news about the AHCA, being trans
will be classified (as one of the many) &amp;ldquo;pre-existing&amp;rdquo; conditions someone can be
denied health insurance based on. The want to wear clothes of the gender you&amp;rsquo;re
transitioning to can also become a &amp;ldquo;problem&amp;rdquo;, making others &amp;ldquo;uncomfortable&amp;rdquo;.
Also, general hostility towards trans people (that I&amp;rsquo;ve read) can make it harder
to find a job, find a place to live, or any array of simple everyday tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trust</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/trust/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 01:20:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Lucrèce Skylar Næss</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/trust/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
      <content>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;preface&#34;&gt;Preface&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a continuation of &lt;a href=&#34;https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/disconnected/post/personal-space/&#34;&gt;a previous post&lt;/a&gt;, wherein we talked
about trust.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;information&#34;&gt;Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m less trusting then I&amp;rsquo;d honestly like to admit. While I feel I can tell
certain close friends some things, I feel as though I can&amp;rsquo;t tell them other
things. Mostly do to feeling self conscious, or not wanting them to find
something out about me. There are a fair few people even in my inner circle of
friends who I would not tell that this blog exists. There are some who I&amp;rsquo;d only
show specific pages to them, trusting them not to look at the rest. My self
consciousness often leads me to be very picky about what information I share
with what people, mostly afraid of how people would react if they knew certain
things about me.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dysphoria Continued: NSFW</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/dysphoria-continued/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 01:58:46 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Lucrèce Skylar Næss</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/dysphoria-continued/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
      <content>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;limbo&#34;&gt;Limbo&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the past few days I&amp;rsquo;ve found myself in a sort of uncomfortable limbo, stuck
between the want to abandon a gender which offers me little comfort, and
identity I have no connection to, or to stick with my current gender in fear of
the social stigmas I may face. Stuck between a rock and a hard place, uncertain
what to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;trapped&#34;&gt;Trapped&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ironically, it&amp;rsquo;s not my sexual organs that bring my discomfort when it comes to
my gender. Rather the hair on my body. Hair on my legs, my face, under my arms,
etc. Combined with the fact that no matter how much I shave, the hair seems to
come back relatively quick. Whether I actually want to change my gender, or
rather just purge my body of unwanted hair is something I&amp;rsquo;ve given lengthy
consideration to. One is a decision that bears much less impactful weight. All
in all, perhaps I&amp;rsquo;d just be happier being a trap then full-on changing my
gender. Regardless, my body hair leaves me feeling uncomfortable and trapped.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;social-stigmatism&#34;&gt;Social Stigmatism&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While changing your name at first may be awkward, it&amp;rsquo;s certainly not as
stigmatized as changing ones gender. In the environment I live in now, I feel
as though transitioning could be social suicide. As a talented soon-to-be
high-school graduate, I would hate to negatively impact my chances at getting
any form of employment or housing. Even worse-yet, having those things yet still
being in a toxic social environment. It&amp;rsquo;d be one thing &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; to have a job or,
house, but another to have a job or live were I&amp;rsquo;m disrespected and treated
horribly by coworkers and neighbors. Though I suppose the latter is better then
having no job or house at all.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Identity and Dissociation</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/identity-and-dissociation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 02:03:09 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Lucrèce Skylar Næss</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/identity-and-dissociation/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
      <content>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/disconnected/post/images/quote.png&#34; alt=&#34;name&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;identity-and-names&#34;&gt;Identity, and Names&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A beautiful quote form a &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.disqus.com/whats-in-a-name-understanding-pseudonyms&#34;&gt;Disqus Blog&lt;/a&gt; post.
In fact I find the quote quite aptly describes me. For example, I detest my
birth name. While people I know in real life use it, when online friends refer
to me by my online pseudonym, for some reason I find it less jarring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I had to guess, the reason for this is because the majority of friends I&amp;rsquo;ve
made throughout my life, have been online, so my sense of identity online
strengthened while I dissociated from my real identity more and more. I never
had a strong sense of personal identity in the first place. I also don&amp;rsquo;t really
remember my &amp;ldquo;childhood&amp;rdquo;. Combined with depersonalization, everything has added
up and I just can&amp;rsquo;t seem to associate my real name with my identity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;identity-and-dissociation&#34;&gt;Identity, and Dissociation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Depersonalization has been haunting me for years, and still is. It has heavily
contributed to the breakdown of my personal identity and &amp;ldquo;numbing&amp;rdquo; of emotions.
How it specifically broke down my sense of identity and emotions, I really
couldn&amp;rsquo;t tell you, mostly because it was over such a period of time. The most
peculiar thing (to me) though is the fact that I can still empathize with others
on a level that I find most can&amp;rsquo;t. At times it does seem like a double edge
sword though, while your ability to empathize is great, you&amp;rsquo;re also faced with
the fact that you feel like you&amp;rsquo;re starved of your own genuine emotions and just
&amp;ldquo;leech&amp;rdquo; off of the emotions of others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;identity-dissociation-and-intimate-relationships&#34;&gt;Identity, Dissociation, and Intimate Relationships&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me, having intimate relationships with others is a struggle. When things are
good, my partner makes me feel just a bit more &amp;ldquo;normal&amp;rdquo;, Though most of the time
I find it hard to shake the feeling of numbness. The numbness becomes
debilitating, eating away at me, and making it generally hard to stay positive.
On top of already being a clingy person, this makes me even more high
maintenance. Though the times I do feel genuinely happy, it&amp;rsquo;s the most blissful
experience ever. Depersonalization usually makes me feel detached from the
social environment I&amp;rsquo;m in. Within the context of day to day things this isn&amp;rsquo;t
really a bother for me most of the time, and I&amp;rsquo;ve adjusted to it. However
feeling distant and disconnected in the presence of my partner is something I&amp;rsquo;ve
never quite adjusted to, and usually makes me feel guilty. My last major
relationship never helped this feeling, as my partner always acted incredibly
distant, and it felt as though we hardly interacted. I ended up mostly blaming
myself for this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;escapism-nsfw&#34;&gt;Escapism: NSFW&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Escapism for me has been used to a chronic degree. I&amp;rsquo;ll admit, my favorite thing
to use for escapism is sex. Whether emotions are involved or not, sex for me has
been my favorite way to manifest escapism. I think I&amp;rsquo;m particularly fond of sex
because in addition to pleasure, it provides me with a distorted sense of
emotions. While in normal day to day activities I find myself disconnected and
numb, when I have sex, I find myself engaged, and happy. Sex is an easy outlet
for escaping from my mental health issues. While I have had genuinely intimate
sex with people in the past, I&amp;rsquo;ve probably had more meaningless sex then I&amp;rsquo;m
willing to admit.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Night owl woes</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/night-owl-woes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2017 01:35:01 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Lucrèce Skylar Næss</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/night-owl-woes/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
      <content>&lt;p&gt;I thought I&amp;rsquo;d write something a bit less heavy this time. I&amp;rsquo;m a &amp;ldquo;night owl&amp;rdquo;,
which if you don&amp;rsquo;t know what that means, I basically am awake mostly in the
afternoon and at very late hours in the night / early morning (the opposite of
most people). I also happen to live in a small town (ironically, the larger in my
county), so there&amp;rsquo;s really nothing much to do at night since the town is &amp;ldquo;dead&amp;rdquo;.
This coupled with the fact that a majority of my local friends are not night
owls often leaves me quite lonely feeling during the night. At times I long to
live somewhere a tad bigger with &lt;sup&gt;24&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;7&lt;/sub&gt; public transportation, so if I felt like
going out somewhere I easily could hop a train or bus to a bigger city and find
something to do.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Space: NSFW</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/personal-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2017 03:37:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Lucrèce Skylar Næss</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/personal-space/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
      <content>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;preface&#34;&gt;Preface&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is going to be another post that just rambles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-bit-of-context&#34;&gt;A bit of context&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I prefer, most of the time, to not have my personal space violated, I&amp;rsquo;d assume
this is the norm among the majority of people. For me it stems from trust issues
that I&amp;rsquo;ve had for quite a while now. I won&amp;rsquo;t scream or pitch a fight if my
personal space is violated, rather I try to tell the person who violated it not
to make the same mistake again. For a while though my anxiousness around being
physical with people was a tad extreme, for example, I was not fond of shaking
hands of acquaintances, not only because my hand-shaking skills are poor, but
my lack of willingness to trust people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;trust-issues&#34;&gt;Trust issues&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My trust issues go back years, mostly due to failed relationships and being
betrayed or abandoned by close friends. One example is a past relationship in
which my partner was verbally and psychologically abusive, and quite often
drunk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;abuse-and-trust-issues&#34;&gt;Abuse and Trust issues&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Going into the relationship the individual was comforting and caring, as I had
just come down from a rough breakup. The first snag in the road came when she
attempted to convert me to Christianity, I tried, mostly for her, but I, being
agnostic (I believe god(s) might exist, but choose to not follow any) never
quite could get myself to believe any of it. This caused her to become &lt;strong&gt;very&lt;/strong&gt;
violent and start to verbally abuse me, I stood up for myself and didn&amp;rsquo;t back
down and eventually she accepted the fact (or just backed down) that I wasn&amp;rsquo;t
religious. After the argument I began to seriously reconsider if I wanted a
relationship with a person who could be so brutal, thought at the time I just
let it slip. We continued to squabble and occasionally quip (over things I can&amp;rsquo;t
remember). After a number of breakups and makeups I decided to just end it for
good. We both were quite damaged people who weren&amp;rsquo;t very compatible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometime after this she ended up meeting a close friend of mine, and more or
less tried to use my friend as bait to get me back in a relationship. This
friend was (and still is) like a daughter to me, so I wasn&amp;rsquo;t having any of this.
After some heated arguments and spectacular spectacles of bullshit, my friend
ended up going offline for a while (months&amp;hellip;possible 3+). This was the final
nail in the coffin to solidify my distrust of her. Not only verbally and
psychologically abusing me, but actively trying to rip apart my social life. I
took my final stand against her bullshit, and more-or-less gave her a taste of
her of medicine, while I&amp;rsquo;m not proud of this, it certainly sent the message to
back off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;divorcing-psychical-intimacy-and-romance-sexuality&#34;&gt;Divorcing psychical intimacy and romance/sexuality&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After that relationship I developed a bit of a &amp;ldquo;hardened&amp;rdquo; outer shell as a
reaction to the trauma I had gone through (much more then I detailed in this
post). I became very picky about who in general had physical contact with me.
This also did lead me to decouple the idea of psychical intimacy and romantic
implications, in that things traditionally thought of to have a sexual/romantic
implication, were just, normal. E.g. if I decide to cuddle someone, there&amp;rsquo;s no
inherent sexual or emotional connotation implied. While I typically only cuddle
people who I trust, I don&amp;rsquo;t see any sexual or romantic connotation in doing so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;physical-contact&#34;&gt;Physical contact&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This section will probably mostly be a list. Firstly, a list of okay things to
do, a general baseline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shake my hand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High five&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pat my shoulder (this one &lt;strong&gt;REALLY&lt;/strong&gt; depends on who you are though)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Things that are okay to do, if I trust you enough (kinda on varying levels).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hug me&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cuddle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lean against&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;poke me&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;stroke my hair&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Massage a majority of my body&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could list more, but to be honest I think it&amp;rsquo;s a pretty typical set of things.
The difference being, I get quite defensive when someone breaks my trust and
touches me in a way I don&amp;rsquo;t like. I don&amp;rsquo;t freak out or scream, but I generally
am &lt;strong&gt;very&lt;/strong&gt; stern with the person and make it quite clear that wasn&amp;rsquo;t okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;summary&#34;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t break my trust by touching me in a way I don&amp;rsquo;t like, I&amp;rsquo;ll be continuing
this post possibly into a second part.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dysphoria: NSFW</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/dysphoria/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 01:55:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Lucrèce Skylar Næss</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/dysphoria/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
      <content>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;preface-nsfw&#34;&gt;Preface: NSFW.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This one might get weird, and rambly. That&amp;rsquo;s the difficulty with writing about
things you don&amp;rsquo;t remember clearly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-gender-dysphoria&#34;&gt;What is Gender Dysphoria?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As not everybody reading this might know what gender dysphoria is right off,
I&amp;rsquo;ll try to provide a simple definition. Gender dysphoria is a condition where
a person emotionally and psychologically identifies as the opposite of one&amp;rsquo;s
biological sex. E.g.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A person who is biologically male would identify as female.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A person who is biologically female would identify as male.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;my-experience-s-with-gender-dysphoria&#34;&gt;My Experience(s) with Gender Dysphoria&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-first-significant-other&#34;&gt;My first Significant Other.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think some of my first experiences with questioning my biological sex was with
my first significant other, who happened to be male. At one point in our
relationship we decided to do some &amp;ldquo;role playing&amp;rdquo;, in which I would usually have
the role of being more feminine and submissive, which included wearing &amp;ldquo;female&amp;rdquo;
clothing. At the time since it was my first time dating another guy in my mind
it reminded me of a heterosexual relationship and it didn&amp;rsquo;t really bother me. I
was rather accepting of being feminine. At the time I just saw it as a way to
spice things up a bit, and not as this thing that made me question quite a bit
about my life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-second-male-significant-other&#34;&gt;My second (male) Significant other.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the time I was dating my second boyfriend I had been through a &lt;strong&gt;Very&lt;/strong&gt; rough
patch in my life, and I just wanted someone who I could depend on. It turned out
that he was (also) rather accepting of the idea of me wearing &amp;ldquo;female&amp;rdquo; clothing.
Though in this relationship it felt less like a kink, and more like wearing
clothes. I again was happy to be feminine around someone. At times though I felt
a disconnect between what my mind thought, and what my body is. I.e. the fact
that I&amp;rsquo;m very feminine, but am in a male body.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-real-eye-opening&#34;&gt;A Real Eye Opening.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One particular relationship I had with a female (who to this day is a good
friend) really made me rethink myself. She was more of a tomboy, and my
feminine tendencies complimented her tomboy-ishness. This was the first time
in my life were I actually seriously considered changing my gender. Though other
things at the time hampered that thinking and it wasn&amp;rsquo;t until I started
meditating as a coping method for some serious issues and trauma I was dealing
with that I again thought about the topic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the time my masculinity was never something that bothered me, nor did the
thought of being feminine. Though occasionally (like most people) I did think
about the subject.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;loss-of-identity-and-dpdr&#34;&gt;Loss of Identity and DPDR.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My DPDR (Depersonalization-derealization disorder) led to worsening identity
issues (which I still struggle with). For years I&amp;rsquo;ve merely just dealt with
not really knowing &amp;ldquo;who I am&amp;rdquo;. Though one moment, for a while, made those years
of trauma melt away. A few friends encouraged me to buy some &amp;ldquo;female&amp;rdquo; clothing
of my own, (as previous female clothing I had worn was typically borrowed). It
was a pair of extra long thigh-highs. When they arrived and I put them on,
something felt, different. Something felt a bit more complete. This led to the
purchase of a garter-belt (to hold the thigh-highs up), and a pleated skater
skirt. While at first the purchasing of this new clothing brought me great joy,
it didn&amp;rsquo;t last long. I had started to semi-seriously think about my gender and
whether or not I&amp;rsquo;d want to change it. One day though, out of the blue, a rather
nasty panic attack hit me. It felt like being hit by a truck, my mind was
racing, with only one thought &amp;ldquo;this isn&amp;rsquo;t right, you aren&amp;rsquo;t the right gender.&amp;rdquo;
and it scared the living shit out of me. Since then I&amp;rsquo;ve had two similar panic
attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;feeling-uncomfortable-in-your-own-skin&#34;&gt;Feeling Uncomfortable in Your Own Skin&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The worst thing to happen after feeling like you&amp;rsquo;ve finally grasped your
identity and gaining a positive body image&amp;hellip;is loosing that sense of identity
all over again. Sometimes I feel &amp;ldquo;fine&amp;rdquo;, and don&amp;rsquo;t really question my gender,
and sometimes I feel like curling up in a ball and tuning out everything because
the anxiety induced by gender dysphoria is so strong.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boop</title>
      <link>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/boop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2017 02:34:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Lucrèce Skylar Næss</author>
      <guid>https://lucynaess.github.io/disconnected/post/boop/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
      <content>&lt;p&gt;First initial test post.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>